[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "NNS", "VBP", "NNS", ",", "RB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 64, "question": "So he was a bit naughty on the facts, wasn't he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 65, "answer": "Well, look, when people give speeches, not every fact is always absolutely accurate.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 97, "question": "What did you make of that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 98, "answer": "I thought that was brilliant.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["United States"], "PERSON": ["Barack Obama", "Barack Obama"]}, "docId": "120829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "RBR", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "WRB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 120, "question": "Are you concerned about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 121, "answer": "Well, they certainly have a lot more than Barack Obama did when Barack Obama got elected president of the United States.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Condoleezza"]}, "docId": "120829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "NNP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 132, "question": "I mean, wouldn't you want her as secretary of state again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 133, "answer": "I had never seen Condoleezza give a political speech.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 134, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 135, "answer": "I mean, she has given a lot of foreign policy addresses.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Placido Domingo"], "PERSON": ["Luciano Pavarotti"]}, "docId": "120829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 140, "question": "Are you a Led Zeppelin, AC/DC man or more of an elevator music guy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 141, "answer": "IULIANI: I am Luciano Pavarotti, Placido Domingo man.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Led Zeppelin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 145, "question": "Does it matter for presidential candidates or running mates, what they listen to on their iPods?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJR", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "VBG", "NNS", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 146, "answer": "It does matter that they listen to music.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 152, "question": "Tomorrow Mitt Romney has got to make the speech of his life, hasn't he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 153, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", ",", "NN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 171, "question": "Governor Luis Fortuno, how are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 172, "answer": "Very well, thank you.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Luis Fortuno"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "EX", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 179, "question": "What was the feeling in the room tonight?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 180, "answer": "ORBETT: Oh, there was electricity in the room.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 188, "question": "A home run for you, too?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 189, "answer": "I believe so, actually.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CD", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 194, "question": "They've got a bit of a point, haven't they?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 195, "answer": "Well, the point is they've had four years to fix it and they haven't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "CD", "NN", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 209, "question": "What advice would you give him if you were having a private conversation with him now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 210, "answer": "Number one issue out there is jobs.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "WRB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 215, "question": "I don't buy it, do you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 216, "answer": "Well, I think once you've been on that stage and you come back to the stage for a moment, you really show how good you are on the stage.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 221, "question": "Are you concerned at all that he may not have the details to back up the bigger broad picture plan?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "DT", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJR", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 222, "answer": "Not at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Romney", "Paul Ryan"]}, "docId": "120829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", ",", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "IN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 229, "question": "What's your sense?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 230, "answer": "Let me tell you, as an Hispanic, when we get around the dinner table, we talk about jobs, we talk about education, to the extent that both Governor Romney and Paul Ryan can deliver a message, a clear message on both issues, that will come across very strongly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 231, "question": "We have heard a lot more, Governor, about Mitt Romney as the man, as the father, as the grandfather, as the husband, is that helping him, do you think, as the American public get to see another side to the guy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "RBR", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 232, "answer": "I think it helps him very much so.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 242, "question": "He has got to rock this crowd tomorrow, hasn't he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 243, "answer": "I agree.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 261, "question": "You must feel at home in a room like this, don't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 262, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "WP", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 325, "question": "How are you going to respond next week?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 326, "answer": "Well, you know, Piers, the conventions aren't just about what happens in the convention hall.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "IN", "DT", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 342, "question": "Now are you joining the party in the Grill now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 343, "answer": "I may for a little bit.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["last night"]}, "docId": "120829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "EX", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 364, "question": "What is the real guy like?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 365, "answer": "I think you saw the real guy there last night.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 372, "question": "Did I say that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 373, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 385, "question": "But he was a bit disingenuous with some facts today, wasn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 386, "answer": "No, he wasn't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 388, "question": "But what about his GM plum that closed under President Bush that he blamed Obama for in?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "IN", "PRP$", "NNP", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "IN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 389, "answer": "I haven't researched that.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["GM"], "PERSON": ["Bush", "Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 395, "question": "What else have you got?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 396, "answer": "That's not bad.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 397, "question": "It's pretty awful to blame him for a plum that closed under the Republican administration?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 398, "answer": "We're talking about big ideas.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}, "docId": "120829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "CD", "NN", "TO", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 411, "question": "Are you concerned that will be perceived as anti-women?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 412, "answer": "I think what the issue is that extremists, when Barack Obama has voted four time to say, if you have a failed abortion and the baby is born alive, you are not allowed to save it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 419, "question": "Is it really advisable to have people like Todd Akin raring their ugly heads coming out with all this gunfire about rape?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 420, "answer": "I was a prosecutor.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Todd Akin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 454, "question": "Why would you do that when they basically want to get rid of you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 455, "answer": "Well, this election is bigger than a single issue.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 460, "question": "Do you believe in gay marriage?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 461, "answer": "I do, I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 462, "question": "And so, how can you really support the ticket which is so resolutely opposed not just the gay marriage, but to most gay right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "NN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "TO", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 463, "answer": "Right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 513, "question": "I mean, don't you know why there is such a disregarded thing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "EX", "VBZ", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 514, "answer": "Well, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 525, "question": "Would you do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 526, "answer": "I would do that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 527, "question": "Jimmy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 528, "answer": "Jobs in the economy first.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 559, "question": "What was your thought?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 560, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 583, "question": "He was pretty disingenuous with the facts, wasn't he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 584, "answer": "Well, this is the point I was going to bring up.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 654, "question": "In he going to nail it, or is he going to be, as he is often with these speeches, a little bit disappointing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "DT", "RB", "NN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 655, "answer": "I saw him four years ago a couple times and he was really boring.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 667, "question": "Maeve, how is he going to appeal to you women like you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 668, "answer": "Well, just on the presentation part.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "CC", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 670, "question": "He would?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "."], "aSentId": 671, "answer": "-- and the chart, the power point.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Maeve"], "PERSON": ["Hillary Clinton"]}, "docId": "120829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ":", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 696, "question": "What are you looking for?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 697, "answer": "I think it's like Maeve said -- he kind of -- there's that old Hillary Clinton, she's got to be likable enough.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 698, "question": "Why don't people like him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 699, "answer": "Because they don't know him.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 721, "question": "Ben?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 722, "answer": "That's not the business I'm in.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 726, "question": "Hit or miss?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "CC", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 727, "answer": "I think he will just hit.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 728, "question": "Ryan?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 729, "answer": "He will probably be a hit.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120829pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", ",", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 731, "question": "Hit or miss?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "CC", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 732, "answer": "Easy audience, probably be a hit.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]